<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nodejs on Sami Jaktholm</title>
    <link>https://sjakthol.github.io/tags/nodejs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nodejs on Sami Jaktholm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sjakthol.github.io/tags/nodejs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>aws-dynamodb-copy</title>
      <link>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/aws-dynamodb-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/aws-dynamodb-copy/</guid>
      <description>aws-dynamodb-copy is a simple script that allows you to copy the contents of a DynamoDB table into another table on the same AWS region.
The script doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide any fancy features. It scans the source table using a parallel scan and writes the items to the target tables in batches. The rate at which items are copied can be tuned to suit the capacity allocated to the target and source tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aws-kms-crypt</title>
      <link>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/aws-kms-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/aws-kms-crypt/</guid>
      <description>aws-kms-crypt is a cross-language utility for managing application secrets within AWS using the KMS service. The key features of this tool are:
Features  Interoperable - Interoperable implementations for Bash, NodeJS, Python and Rust. Secure - AES encryption with KMS generated data keys. Simple - Simple API for encrypting and decrypting sensitive data in all supported languages.  Installation  Node.js module in NPM: https://www.npmjs.com/package/aws-kms-crypt Python package in PyPi: https://pypi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cfn-execute-change-set</title>
      <link>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/cfn-execute-changeset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/cfn-execute-changeset/</guid>
      <description> cfn-execute-change-set is a command line utility for reviewing and executing AWS CloudFormation change sets. The tool parses the output of AWS CLI create-change-set command, prints out a summary of changes and executes the change set if so instructed.
This utility requires Node.js and can be installed with npm:
npm install -g cfn-execute-change-set  Links  Package in NPM: https://www.npmjs.com/package/cfn-execute-change-set  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cfn-monitor</title>
      <link>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/cfn-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjakthol.github.io/projects/cfn-monitor/</guid>
      <description> cfn-monitor is a command line utility for monitoring the progress of CloudFormation stack operations. The tool parses the output of the AWS CLI create-stack and update-stack commands, listens for the stack events of the affected stacks and prints them out to the terminal as they occur.
This utility requires Node.js and can be installed with npm:
npm install -g cfn-monitor  Links  Package in NPM: https://www.npmjs.com/package/cfn-monitor  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>